We're here in the reality of life,
With all the nature around us
We see
That the day will come when we're gone
And all this will still be here.
About this situation
Rabbi Nachman says:
That when one find oneself
In dire straits,
When he can't go on
Since life is hard,
There are harder times
And easier times,
If he remembers the afterlife,
Which will come 40 years later
When he's in the grave,
And they let him out to such a place
What's the first thing he'll do?
Let's say it isn't 40 years later,
Let's say he has half an hour to live
What will he do?
Everyone has a different idea.
He has half an hour to do something
If he comes to a place like this
He can get in touch with god,
He can pray,
He can spend that time
In a calm, positive place,
In Sacher Park.